A Guide to the Correspondence Files of Special Collections, University of Virginia Library 1931-1990s
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Correspondence (General)
  - Rare Books Dept. Correspondence (miscellaneous)
    - Tenyson-Hallam Poems (see also: Hallam) (Box A35-18B)
    - Tension Envelope Co. (Box A35-18B)
    - Tetley, Gerard (Box A35-18B)
    - Texas (Box A35-18B)
    - Texas University (Box A35-18B)
    - Textbooks, Virginia (see: grammars - Virginia) (Box A35-18B)
    - Thomas, Alan G. (Box A35-18B)
    - Thomas, Kate (Mrs. C. R.) (Box A35-18B)
    - Thomas, Essell (Box A35-18B)
    - Thomas, Mrs. H. Rogers (Box A35-18B)
    - Thompson, Frank T. (Box A35-18B)
    - Thompson, Lawrance (Box A35-18B)
    - Thompson, Lawrence S. (Box A35-18B)
    - Thoreau (Box A35-18B)
    - The Thoreau Society (Box A35-18B)
    - Thornton, Neal Blair (Box A35-18B)
    - Thornton and Fisher maps (Box A35-18B)
    - Thorsen, W.B. (Box A35-18B)
    - Thurber, Cleveland (Box A35-18B)
    - Tinker, William (Box A35-18B)
    - Todd, John (Box A35-18B)
    - Todd, William B. (Box A35-18B)
    - Toledano, Ben C. (Box A35-18B)
    - Tompkins (Box A35-18B)
    - Tompkins, Elizabeth N. (Box A35-18B)
    - Tompkins, Willis W. (Box A35-18B)
    - Tonson (Box A35-18B)
    - Toombs, Kenneth S. (Box A35-18B)
    - Torrence, Clayton (Box A35-18B)
    - Towler, William R. (Box A35-18B)
    - Townes, William (Box A35-18B)
    - Transportation Services Division (Box A35-18B)
    - Trips - pending (Box A35-18B)
    - Travel Budget (Box A35-18C)
    - Travel Plans (Box A35-18C)
    - Travel Regulations (Box A35-18C)
    - Travel Vouchers (Box A35-18C)
    - Travel Vouchers Wm. H. Runge (Box A35-18C)
    - Travel Vouchers - Neal Thornton (Box A35-18C)
    - Tree, Roland (see also: Henry Stevens Son & Stiles) (Box A35-18C)
    - Trollope, Anthoony (Box A35-18D)
    - Trollope List (Box A35-18D)
    - Trollope Presentation and Dinner (Box A35-18D)
    - Troubs, D.S. (Box A35-18D)
    - Truitt, Mrs. Garland L. (Box A35-18D)
    - Tuck, Theodore E. (Chas. H Bohn, etc) (Box A35-18D)
    - Tucker, Mrs. Albert S.J., Sr. - "Summary View..., 1971" (Box A35-18D)
    - Tucker, George (Box A35-18D)
    - Tuggle, Harry Irvine, Jr. (Box A35-18D)
    - Tuition Reimbursement Program (Box A35-18D)
    - Turnbull, Robert J. (see also: Stuart Jackson) (Box A35-18D)
    - Turner, Dechard, Jr. (see also: Dallas Public Library) (Box A35-18D)
    - Turner, Robert H. (Box A35-18D)
    - Turner, Robert K. (Box A35-18D)
    - Turner, Robert K., Jr. (Box A35-18D)
    - Tuskegee Institute (Box A35-18D)
    - Tuttle, Charles E., Company (Box A35-18D)
    - Tuttle, Lucille (Box A35-18D)
    - Tuttle, Stephen D. (Box A35-18D)
    - Tutwiler, Carrington C. (Box A35-18D)
    - Twain, Mark (Box A35-18D)
    - Twyman, Dr. & Mrs. James B. (Box A35-18D)
    - Typesetting (Box A35-18D)
    - Typophiles (Box A35-18D)
    - Typography (Box A35-18D)
    - U - General (Box A35-18E)
    - Ulster County Gazette (Box A35-18E)
    - Undergraduate - Readers Library (Box A35-18E)
    - Union Club Exhibit (Box A35-18E)
    - U.S. Information Agency (Box A35-18E)
    - U.S. Savings Bond (Box A35-18E)
    - University of Chicago (Box A35-18E)
    - University of Florida (Libraries) (Box A35-18E)
    - University of Iowa (Box A35-18E)
    - University of Maryland (Box A35-18E)
    - University of North Carolina (Box A35-18E)
    - University of Pennsylvania (Box A35-18E)
    - [University of Virginia] University Press (Box A35-18E)
    - University Presses (Box A35-18E)
    - University Printing Office - requisition forms (Box A35-18E)
    - University of South Carolina (Box A35-18E)
    - University of Tennessee (Box A35-18E)
    - University of Toronto (Box A35-18E)
    - University of Virginia - Faculty Minutes (Box A35-18E)
    - University of Virginia - Alumni Association (Box A35-18F)
    - University of Virginia Alumni Fund (Box A35-18F)
    - University of Virginia Food Service (Box A35-18F)
    - University of Virginia Graduate School of Arts & Sciences (Box A35-18F)
    - University of Virginia History - Source (Box A35-18F)
    - University of Virginia - Hospital (Box A35-18F)
    - University of Virginia Library - Stack addition (Box A35-18F)
    - University of Virginia Library - Statistics (Box A35-18F)
    - University of Virginia Magazine (Box A35-18F)
    - University of Virginia - Miscellaneous (Brown, Corderman, Shannon, Vining) (Box A35-18F)
    - University Microfilms - Ann Arbor (Box A35-18F)
    - University Mail Service (Box A35-18F)
    - University of Virginia - Press Corres. (1953- ) (Box A35-18F)
    - University of Virginia Railway Historical Society (Box A35-18F)
    - University of Virginia Research Funds (Box A35-18F)
    - University of Virginia - Seal (Box A35-18F)
    - University of Virginia - Security Office (Box A35-18F)
    - [University of Virginia] Student Aid & Placement (Box A35-18F)
    - Work-Study Program (Box A35-18F)
    - University of Wisconsin (Box A35-18F)
    - Unwanted (Box A35-18F)
    - V - General (Box A35-18G)
    - Vacant Positions (Box A35-18G)
    - Vail, R.W.G. (Box A35-18G)
    - Vance, Joe (Box A35-18G)
    - Van De Camp, Peter (Box A35-18G)
    - Van Devanter, Willis (Box A35-18G)
    - Vann, Elizabeth C. Denny (Box A35-18G)
    - Varma, D.P. (Box A35-18G)
    - Vaughan, Joseph (Box A35-18G)
    - Vault (Box A35-18G)
    - Vellum Binding (Box A35-18G)
    - Vellum, Books Published on (Box A35-18G)
    - Verner, Coolie (Box A35-18G)
    - Virgil (Box A35-18G)
    - Virginia Arms (Box A35-18G)
    - Virginia - Books before 1800 (Box A35-18G)
    - Virginia - Book collectors (Box A35-18G)
    - Virginia Book Company (Box A35-18G)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University (Box A35-18G)
    - Virginia - Buildings (Box A35-18G)
    - Virginia Gazette Ledgers (Box A35-18G)
    - Virginia Historical Society (see also: Patrick Henry) (Box A35-18G)
    - Virginia History Federation (Box A35-18G)
    - Virginia Journalists (Box A35-18G)
    - VLA - Virginia Library Association Activities Committee (Box A35-18G)
    - VLA - Virginia Library Association (Box A35-18G)
    - Manuscripts - Transfers (Box A35-18G)
    - Serials Cataloguing Procedures and Helpful Hints (Box A35-18G)
    - Virginia - maps (Box A35-18H)
    - Virginia Military Institute (Box A35-18H)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (Box A35-18H)
    - Virginia - Newspapers (Box A35-18H)
    - Virginia - Opera (Box A35-18H)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box A35-18H)
    - Virginia Press Assoc. (Box A35-18H)
    - Virginia Printmakers Exhibition (Box A35-18H)
    - Virginia Ruralist (Box A35-18H)
    - Virginia - Governors Office (Box A35-18H)
    - Virginia - Libraries (Box A35-18H)
    - Virginia - State Documents (Box A35-18H)
    - Virginia State Library (Box A35-18H)
    - University of Virginia Library - Guide (Box A35-18H)
    - Visiting Committee for the University of Virginia Library (Box A35-18H)
    - Vosper, Robert (Box A35-18H)
    - W - General - Rare Books 1956-1967 (Box A35-18H)
    - Correspondence - Serials Cataloguing (Box A35-18H)
    - Procedures (Box A35-18H)
    - W - General 1968-1986 (Box A35-18I)
    - Wagner, Clarence W. (Box A35-18I)
    - Wainwright, Alexander D. (Box A35-18I)
    - Wainwright, Nicholas B. (Box A35-18I)
    - Walbridge, Earle (Box A35-18I)
    - Walden / Henry D. Thoreau (Box A35-18I)
    - Wallace, Wayne A. (Box A35-18I)
    - Walpole, Hugh (Box A35-18I)
    - The Walpole Society (Box A35-18I)
    - Walters Art Gallery (Box A35-18I)
    - Walton, Harry A. (see also: Hobbes) (Box A35-18I)
    - Walton, Isaak (Box A35-18I)
    - Wangler, John (Box A35-18I)
    - Warren, James R., Sr. (Box A35-18I)
    - Warren, Yolanda (Box A35-18I)
    - Washington, George (Box A35-18I)
    - Washington, George - portrait (Box A35-18I)
    - Washington Library - Mt. Vernon Room (Box A35-18I)
    - Washington Library - Reproduction of at University of Virginia (brochures) (Box A35-18I)
    - Washington & Lee University (see also: Ollinger Crenshaw) (Box A35-18I)
    - Washington University Library (Box A35-18I)
    - Waters, D.W. (Box A35-18I)
    - Watson, Edwin M. ("Pa") - papers of (Box A35-18I)
    - Watts, G. Martin Brill (Box A35-18I)
    - Watts, Mrs. Steve (Box A35-18I)
    - Wayland (Box A35-18I)
    - Wayne State University (Box A35-18I)
    - Wearstler, Helen F. (Box A35-18J)
    - Weather Conditions (Emergency) (Box A35-18J)
    - "Weather Rule" (Box A35-18J)
    - Weatherly, John Robert (Box A35-18J)
    - Webb (Box A35-18J)
    - Webb, Joseph P. (Box A35-18J)
    - Webb, Robert (Box A35-18J)
    - Weber, Carl J. (Box A35-18J)
    - Webner, Mr. & Mrs. W. Gordon (Box A35-18J)
    - Webster, Noah (Box A35-18J)
    - Weeks, Mangum (Box A35-18J)
    - Wellford, T. Dabney (Box A35-18J)
    - Wenning, Henry (Box A35-18J)
    - Wertenbaker, Thomas J. (Box A35-18J)
    - West, Davenport (Box A35-18J)
    - West, Frank A. (Box A35-18J)
    - Westerfield, Peggy (Box A35-18J)
    - West Indies (see also: Robert Fisher - Jamaica Journal) (Box A35-18J)
    - West Virginia University (Box A35-18J)
    - Westall (Box A35-18J)
    - Wharton, Edith (Box A35-18J)
    - Whitman, Walt (Box A35-18J)
    - Whitmore, Mrs. H. Bruce (Box A35-18J)
    - Whittet, Robert, Sr. (Box A35-18J)
    - White, Mr. & Mrs. William - gifts 1988 (Box A35-18J)
    - Littleton Wickham Library (Box A35-18J)
    - Wilder, Thornton (Box A35-18K)
    - Wiley, Keith B. (Box A35-18K)
    - Wilkin, Robert (Box A35-18K)
    - Wilkins, W.B. (see also: Map collections) (Box A35-18K)
    - College of William and Mary (Box A35-18K)
    - William, father, pseud. (Box A35-18K)
    - Williams College (Box A35-18K)
    - Williams, Harris H. (Box A35-18K)
    - Williams, Langbourne M. (Box A35-18K)
    - Williamsburg Imprints (Box A35-18K)
    - Wilson, B.W., Paper Co. (Box A35-18K)
    - Wilson, Cora McDevitt (Box A35-18K)
    - Wilson, Harry Minor (Box A35-18K)
    - Wilson, James Southall - see Charles M. Davison, Jr. (Box A35-18K)
    - Wilson Display Material (Box A35-18K)
    - Wilson, Woodrow (Box A35-18K)
    - Winchester, Virginia (Box A35-18K)
    - Winchester Imprints (see also: John Heiskell) (Box A35-18K)
    - Windecker, William (Box A35-18K)
    - Wing, Donald (Box A35-18K)
    - Wingo, John T. (Box A35-18K)
    - Winsett, Marvin Davis (Box A35-18K)
    - Winterich, John T. (Box A35-18K)
    - Winterthur Museum (Box A35-18K)
    - Winton, Calhoun (Box A35-18K)
    - Wisconsin State Historical Society (Box A35-18K)
    - Wolf, Edwin (Box A35-18K)
    - Wood, Mrs. Arthur (Box A35-18K)
    - Wood, David J., Jr. (Box A35-18K)
    - Wood, E.R. (Box A35-18K)
    - Wood, James (Box A35-18K)
    - Woolf, Virginia (Box A35-18K)
    - Work-Study - Time Reports (Box A35-18K)
    - Workmen's Compensation (Box A35-18K)
    - Wormser (Box A35-18K)
    - Wranek, William H. (Box A35-18L)
    - Wroth (Box A35-18L)
    - Wright Bibliography American Fiction (Box A35-18L)
    - Wright, Mrs. Edward P. (Box A35-18L)
    - Wright, James E. (Box A35-18L)
    - Wright, Lyle H. (Box A35-18L)
    - Wright, Louise L. (Mrs. Quincy) (Box A35-18L)
    - Wright, William D. (Box A35-18L)
    - Wroth (Box A35-18L)
    - Wyllie, George (Box A35-18L)
    - Wyllie, Mrs. John Cook (Box A35-18L)
    - Wyllie, John Cook (Box A35-18L)
    - Wyllie, Mabel (Box A35-18L)
    - Wynne, Marjorie Gray (Box A35-18L)
    - Wytheville (Box A35-18L)
    - Xerox (Box A35-18L)
    - Ximenes: Rare Books Shop (Box A35-18L)
    - Y - General 1965-1982 (Box A35-18L)
    - Yale University (Box A35-18L)
    - Yeats, William Butler (Box A35-18L)
    - Yenawine, Wayne S. (Box A35-18L)
    - Yoe, John H. (Box A35-18L)
    - Young (Box A35-18L)
    - Young, A. Churchill (see also: Ellis-Munford Papers) (Box A35-18L)
    - Younger, Edward E. (Box A35-18L)
    - Z - General 1967-1979 (Box A35-18L)
    - Zehmer, George B. (Box A35-18L)
  - Invoices
    - Invoices - Associates Endow. (ALEMS) (Box A35-18L)
    - Invoices - Associates Endowment (ALEM2) (Box A35-18L)
    - Invoices - Alumni Barrett (ALUM2) (Box A35-18L)
    - Invoices - B-Barrett (BBAR) (Box A35-18M)
    - Invoices - Barrett (BBAR2) (Box A35-18M)
    - Invoices - Anon McGregor Lib. (BRMC2) (Box A35-18M)
    - Invoices - Bruce McGregor (BRMCG) (Box A35-18M)
    - Invoices - Bruce McGregor (BRMC2) (Box A35-18M)
    - Invoices - Bruce (BRUCE2) (Box A35-18M)
    - Invoices - B - Special Collections (B-SPEC) (Box A35-18M)
    - Invoices - B - Special Collections (B-SPEC2) (Box A35-18M)
    - Invoices - Cohn - Hemingway (COHN) (Box A35-18N)
    - Invoices - Coles, E. C. (COLE2) (Box A35-18N)
    - Invoices - Faulkner Collection (FAUCO) (Box A35-18N)
    - Invoices - Faulkner Foundation (FAUFO) (Box A35-18N)
    - Invoices - Henry Gordon (HGRDN) (Box A35-18N)
    - Invoices - Green - Spec. Coll. (GRESC) (Box A35-18N)
    - Invoices - Hatfield - Chappell (HATCH) (Box A35-18N)
    - Invoices - Chappell, Hatfield (HATC2) (Box A35-18N)
    - Invoices - Kimball (KIMBL) (Box A35-18N)
    - Invoices - McGregor Grant (McGR5) (Box A35-18N)
    - Invoices - Linton R. Massey (LMASY) (Box A35-18N)
    - Invoices - Misc. Library Funds (Box A35-18N)
    - Invoices - MOORE2 (Box A35-18N)
    - Invoices - Newcomb (NEWC) (Box A35-18O)
    - Invoices - Newcomb Hall (NEW2) (Box A35-18O)
    - Invoices - O'Neal Rare Book Acct. (ORBA) (Box A35-18O)
    - Invoices - OPPOR (Box A35-18O)
    - Invoices - Price Taylor (PRTAY) (Box A35-18O)
    - Invoices - RBR S and S (RBRSS) (Box A35-18O)
    - Invoices - RHOD2 (Box A35-18O)
    - Invoices - Ribble (Box A35-18O)
    - Invoices - Marion duPont Scott (SCOTT) (Box A35-18O)
    - Invoices - Marion duPont Scott (SCOT2) (Box A35-18O)
    - Invoices - Taylor Collection (TAYCO) (Box A35-18P)
    - Invoices - TREE (Box A35-18P)
    - Invoices - Tunstall, Robert & Virginia (TUNTR) (Box A35-18P)
    - Invoices - Wyllie (WYLIE) (Box A35-18P)
    - Invoices - Multiple Funds (MULTI2) (Box A35-18Q)
    - Invoices - Spec. Gifts -Spec. Coll. (SGS2) (Box A35-18Q)
  - Serials / Periodicals - Master List (Box A35-18Q)
  - Add Lists sent to Serials Cataloging (Box A35-18Q)
  - Alderman Library - Rare Book Department (Box A35-18Q)
  - Bibliographies (Box A35-18Q)
  - Binding - Forms (Box A35-18Q)
  - Binding - Instructions and Lists (Box A35-18Q)
  - Binding - Complete and Pending (Box A35-18Q)
  - Claims and Requests and Cancellations (Box A35-18Q)
  - Correspondence 1982-1989 (Box A35-18Q)
  - Correspondence - Kardex (Box A35-18Q)
  - Sotheby's / AB Bookman's Weekly - Dealers Catalogs (Box A35-18R)
  - Transfer Memos (Box A35-18R)
  - Grolier Club - Correspondence (1956- ) (Box A35-18R)
  - Grolier Club Meeting Charlottesville (A - Z) 1958 (Box A35-18R)
  - H - General 1946-1954 (Box A35-18R)
  - H - General 1955-1959 (Box A35-18S)
  - H - General 1930-1945 (Box A35-18S)
  - H - General (1980- ) (Box A35-18S)
  - H - General 1960-1979 (Box A35-18T)
  - Haiti (Box A35-18T)
  - Assorted Financial Matters (Box A35-18T)
  - Equipment - Inspections (Box A35-18T)
  - Fans - on Alderman Library Roof (Box A35-18T)
- Series II: Patron-Use Files, (1991- )
  - Special Collections Dept. Manuscripts (1996- )
    - Patron Collection Request Slips (MSS) 1996 Jul - 1997 Jun (Box A29-18R)
    - Patron Collection Request Slips (MSS) 1996 Jul - 1997 Jun (Box A36-12M)
    - Patron Registrations (MSS) 1996 Jul - 1997 Jun (Box A29-18S)
      alphabetical A - L
    - Patron Registrations (MSS) 1996 Jul - 1997 Jun (Box A29-18T)
      alphabetical K - Z
    - Patron Collection Request Slips (MSS) 1997 Jul - 1998 Jun (Box A27-16B)
    - Patron Collection Request Slips (MSS) 1997 Jul - 1998 Jun (Box A27-16C)
    - Patron Registrations (MSS) 1997 Jul - 1998 Jun (Box A27-16C)
      alphabetical A - Ba
    - Patron Registrations (MSS) 1997 Jul - 1998 Jun (Box A27-16D)
      alphabetical Be - Le
    - Patron Registrations 1997 Jul - 1998 Jun (Box A27-16E)
      alphabetical Li - Z
    - Patron Request Slips (MSS) 1999 Jul - 2000 Jun (Box A36-13H)
    - Patron Request Slips 1999 Jul - Jun 2000 (Box A36-13I)
    - Patron Request Slips (RBR) 1999 Jul - 1999 Dec (Box A36-13J)
    - Patron Request Slips (RBR) 2000 Jan - 2000 Jun (Box A36-13K)
    - Patron Request Slips (RBR) 2000 Jul - 2000 Nov (Box A36-14D)
    - Patron Request Slips (RBR) 2000 Dec - 2001 Jun (Box A36-14E)
    - Patron Request Slips (MSS) 2000 Jul - 2001 Jun (Box A36-14F)
    - Patron Request Slips (MSS) 2000 Jul - 2001 Jun (Box A36-14G)
    - Patron Request Slips (MSS) 1998 Jul - 1999 Jun (Box A36-12O)
    - Patron Request Slips (MSS) 1998 Jul - 1999 Jun (Box A36-12P)
  - Rare Books Dept. Patron Request Slips 1991 Jul - 1998 Jun
    - Patron Request Slips 1991 Jul - Dec (Box A36-11L)
    - Patron Request Slips 1992 Jan - Apr (Box A36-11M)
    - Patron Request Slips 1992 May - Dec (Box A36-11N)
    - Patron Request Slips 1993 Jan - Jun (Box A36-11O)
    - Patron Request Slips 1993 Jul - Dec (Box A36-11P)
    - Patron Request Slips 1994 Jan - Jun (Box A36-11Q)
    - Patron Request Slips 1994 Jul - Dec (Box A36-11R)
    - Patron Request Slips 1995 Jan - Jul (Box A36-11S)
    - Patron Request Slips 1995 Aug - Dec (Box A36-11T)
    - Patron Request Slips 1996 Jan - Jun (Box A36-12A)
    - Patron Request Slips 1996 Jul - Dec (Box A36-12B)
    - Patron Request Slips 1997 Jan - Jun (Box A36-12C)
    - Patron Request Slips 1997 Jul - Dec (Box A36-12D)
    - Patron Request Slips 1998 Jan - Jun (Box A36-12E)
    - Patron Request Slips 1998 Jul - Dec (Box A36-12F)
  - Patron sign-in logbooks for SC 1996-97, 1997-98, 1998-99 (Box A36-12Q)
- Series III: Manuscripts Field Agent's Files
  - Field Agent's files [1960's - 1970's]:
    - WHW personal [William Grady Ray] (Box A36-12R)
    - University of Virginia Art Objects Survey (Box A36-12R)
    - Policies - Deeds & Appraisers (Box A36-12R)
    - Travel (Box A36-12R)
    - Manuscripts Dept. Publicity (Box A36-12R)
    - Manuscripts Department Collecting Policies (Box A36-12R)
    - Collection Development - Policy statements, memos, etc. (Box A36-12R)
    - Publicity & Public Relations (Box A36-12R)
    - Contact Materials - University of Virginia produced (Box A36-12R)
    - Preservation of MSS - T.J. on, etc. (Box A36-12R)
    - Leads (Box A36-12R)
    - Leads to be followed up (Box A36-12R)
  - Field Agent's files [1960's - 1970's]:
    - COF - Possible (alphabetical A - Z) (Box A36-12S)
    - Collecting Operations Forms for potential MSS collections (Box A36-12S)
  - Field Agent's files [1960's - 1970's]:
    - COF - Sought (alphabetical A - N) (Box A36-12T)
    - Collecting Operations Forms for MSS collections solicited (Box A36-12T)
  - Field Agent's files [1960's - 1970's]:
    - COF - Sought (alphabetical O - Z) (Box A36-13A)
    - Collecting Operations Forms for MSS collections solicited (Box A36-13A)
    - University of Virginia Chronological File Survey (Box A36-13A)
  - Field Agent's files [1960's - 1970's]:
    - Virginia Regional Bibliography (Box A36-13B)
    - Virginia Survey of Primary Sources (Box A36-13B)
    - Virginia Biographical Register (Box A36-13B)
    - Collecting Operations Forms [blanks] (Box A36-13B)
    - COF Priorities Forms - blank (Box A36-13B)
    - Collecting Policies re: Other Institutions (Box A36-13B)
    - Manuscript Department Collections - Possible (Box A36-13B)
    - Files - Organization of (Box A36-13B)
    - Southeastern Architectural Archives (Box A36-13B)
    - Virginia Labor Unions (Box A36-13B)
    - Senators (Box A36-13B)
    - Transportation, History of - Collecting (Box A36-13B)
    - Virginia MSS Sources - Guide (Box A36-13B)
    - Donor Solicitations (Box A36-13B)
    - Long Term Continuity (Box A36-13B)
    - Leads, (2 folders) (Box A36-13B)
- Series IV: Special Collections Student Assistants and Employee Files
  - Student employees, A - F (Box A36-13L)
  - Student employees, G - L (Box A36-13M)
  - Student employees, M - R (Box A36-13N)
  - Student employees, S - Z (Box A36-13O)